[
    {
        "question": " Q.1 What temperature does water boil at?",
        "optionA": "a) 50 degrees Celcius",
        "optionB": "b) 25 degrees Celcius",
        "optionC": "c) 100 degrees Celcius",
        "optionD": "d) 150 degrees Celcius",
        "answer": "c) 100 degrees Celcius"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.2 Who wrote Julius Caesar, Macbeth and Hamlet?",
        "optionA": "a) Wole Soyinka",
        "optionB": "b) William Shakespeare",
        "optionC": "c) Ngozi Chimamanda Adichie",
        "optionD": "d) Dan Brown",
        "answer": "b) William Shakespeare"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.3 What did the crocodile swallow in Peter Pan?",
        "optionA": "a) A Book",
        "optionB": "b) A Computer",
        "optionC": "c) A pair of shoes",
        "optionD": "d) Alarm Clock",
        "answer": "d) Alarm Clock"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.4 Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "a) Dog",
        "optionB": "b) Elephant",
        "optionC": "c) Goat",
        "optionD": "d) Lion",
        "answer": "b) Elephant"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.5 Who lived at 221B, Baker Street, London?",
        "optionA": "a) Tony Stark",
        "optionB": "b) Morgan Freeman",
        "optionC": "c) Sherlock Holmes",
        "optionD": "d) Samuel L. Jackson",
        "answer": "c) Sherlock Holmes"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.6 What colour is a panda?",
        "optionA": "a) Green and Yellow",
        "optionB": "b) Blue and Red",
        "optionC": "c) Green and White",
        "optionD": "d) Black and White",
        "answer": "d) Black and White"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.7 Where is the smallest bone in the human body?",
        "optionA": "a) The Chest",
        "optionB": "b) The Ear",
        "optionC": "c) The Legs",
        "optionD": "d) The Hands",
        "answer": "b) The Ear"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.8 What does the roman numeral C represent?",
        "optionA": "a) 100",
        "optionB": "b) 10",
        "optionC": "c) 10,000",
        "optionD": "d) 1,000,000",
        "answer": "a) 100"
    },

    {
        "question": " Q.9 What takes place in Hong Kong's Happy Valley?",
        "optionA": "a) Chicken Wrestling",
        "optionB": "b) Horse racing",
        "optionC": "c) Street Racing",
        "optionD": "d) Arm Wrestling",
        "answer": "b) Horse racing"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.10 Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
        "optionA": "a) Alexander Graham Bell",
        "optionB": "b) Sir Isaac Newton",
        "optionC": "c) Leonardo Da Vinci",
        "optionD": "d) Albert Einstein",
        "answer": "c) Leonardo Da Vinci"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.11 What’s the most important book in the Moslem religion?",
        "optionA": "a) The Koran",
        "optionB": "b) The Dictionary",
        "optionC": "c) The Bible",
        "optionD": "d) The Chemistry text Book",
        "answer": "a) The Koran"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.12 What’s the capital of Ethiopia?",
        "optionA": "a) Cape Town",
        "optionB": "b) San Francisco",
        "optionC": "c) Addis Ababa",
        "optionD": "d) Syndey",
        "answer": "c) Addis Ababa"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.13 How many squares are there on a chess board?",
        "optionA": "a) 128",
        "optionB": "b) 64",
        "optionC": "c) 32",
        "optionD": "d) 256",
        "answer": "b) 64"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.14 Who invented the electric light bulb?",
        "optionA": "a) Tom Cruise",
        "optionB": "b) Barack Obama",
        "optionC": "c) Wole Soyinka",
        "optionD": "d) Thomas Edison",
        "answer": "d) Thomas Edison"
    },

    {
        "question": "Q.15 What are the first three words of the bible?",
        "optionA": "a) be with everyone",
        "optionB": "b) Again Jesus asked",
        "optionC": "c) In the beginning",
        "optionD": "d) At that time",
        "answer": "c) In the beginning"
    }
]